(Sheldon:)I have a question
about Batman.
(Sheldon:)Batman is a man
who dresses up like a bat.
(Sheldon:)Man-bat is a part man,
part bat hybrid.
(Sheldon:)Now,
(Sheldon:)if Man-Bat dressed up as a man
to fight crime,
(Sheldon:)would he be Man-Batman?
(Leonard:)No, he'd be Bat-Man-Bat.
(Raj:)But wouldn't Man-Batman
just be a Batman
(Raj:)that was bitten by
a radioactive man?
(Howard:)But Batman is a man.
(Howard:)You're talking about a man who
would have the powers of a man.
(Howard:)That's just Man-Man.
(Sheldon:)Well, isn't Man-Man just Man?
(Leonard:)But what if Man-Man
dressed as a bat?
(Raj:)Well, that's just Batman.
(Leonard:)No, if a man dresses as a bat,
(Leonard:)that's Batman,
but if Man-Man dresses as a bat,
(Leonard:)that's Batman-Man.
(cell phone chimes)
(Howard:)So does that answer
your question?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I haven't asked it yet.
(Raj(checking text on phone):)Oh, that's Claire.
Got to run.
(Leonard:)I thought you were back
with Emily.
(Raj:)Uh, actually I'm...
seeing both of them.
(Leonard:)You mean like through their
window from behind a bush?
(Raj:)No, I'm actually dating
two women.
(Raj:)Later.
(chuckles)
Really?
(Leonard:)The guy who for years
couldn't even talk to women
(Leonard:)is suddenly going out
with two of them?
(Leonard:)How is that possible?
WOLOWITZ: I know.
(Howard:)Scientists have tried
to reproduce it
(Howard:)with computational models,
(Howard:)but, in each case,
the world blows up.
(Leonard:)Seriously, that guy's
dating two women?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪